patchworkposse.com 2015-06-13

# Privacy Policies and Disclosures -

[__  Home](http://www.patchworkposse.com/) / Privacy Policies and Disclosures

**Affiliate Marketing**

I participate in affiliate marketing programs where I receive a small commission when products are purchased through links on my blog. I appreciate when you click on those links because they help support me so I can keep designing and writing on Patchwork Posse.

**What information does Patchwork Posse collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.  When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**Does Patchwork Posse use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

****Because Patchwork Posse values your privacy I’ve taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Patchwork Posse therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

<http://www.patchworkposse.com/contact/>

This policy is powered by Trust Guard, {with a few tweaks by Becky}
